You know that feeling.
你都知道那种感觉。
You‘re stuck in bumper-to-bumper traffic.
你被困在水泄不通的交通中。
It’s going to be hours before you get home.
要过好几个小时才能到家。
We all know that congestion is one of the downsides of modern city life.
我们都非常清楚，交通拥堵是现代城市生活的弊端之一。
Don‘t you wish you could take to the skies and zoom above it all in a helicopter?
你难道不希望自己能飞上天空，乘坐直升机在高空之上翱翔吗？
Well, wish no more.
好了，别再空想了。
Right now, the race is on to release the first commercially viable sky taxi.
目前，各方正在竞相推出首款具有商业可行性的空中出租车。
No longer will personal air travel be the preserve of the super wealthy, say optimistic tech entrepreneurs.
乐观的科技企业家们说，个人空中旅行将不再是超级富豪的专属。
There’s just one catch: how do you feel about having no pilot?
但有一个问题：没有飞行员，你会作何感想呢？
For brave passengers, the city of Dubai plans to roll out rides on their pilotless drone taxi project by the end of this year.
对于勇敢的乘客来说，迪拜市计划在今年年底推出他们的无人驾驶无人机出租车项目。
You can buckle up and share the ride with one other passenger in their 18-rotor craft, developed by German start-up Volocopter, with a top speed of 100km/h and a flight time of around 30 minutes.
你可以系好安全带，和另一名乘客一起乘坐由德国初创公司Volocopter开发的18旋翼飞行器，其最高时速为100公里，飞行时间约为30分钟。
If you have more friends, French aviation company Airbus are working on a drone which can carry four to six customers.
如果你有更多朋友，法国空中客车航空公司正在研发一种可以搭载四到六名乘客的无人机。
Or if you prefer your own company, Chinese firm Ehang are pioneering a single-seater drone, which stays airborne for 23 minutes.
或者，如果你更喜欢独自乘坐，中国公司亿航正在开创一种单座无人机，它可以在空中飞行23分钟。
Ride-hailing company Uber also want a piece of the action.
叫车服务公司优步也想分一杯羹。
They say drones like this are the “future of on-demand urban air transportation”.
他们说，这样的无人机是“按需城市空中交通的未来”。
They recently poached NASA chief technologist Mark Moore to help them develop a drone taxi.
他们最近挖走了美国国家航空航天局的首席技术专家马克·摩尔来帮助他们开发无人机出租车。
And he claims it won‘t cost the earth.
而且他声称这不会是天价花费。
Moore told the BBC that with three or four passengers sharing, it would be “very similar to what an UberX [car] costs today”.
摩尔告诉BBC，有三到四名乘客分摊费用的话，费用将“和现在乘坐优步X[汽车]的费用非常相似”。
So far so good.
到目前为止一切顺利。
But naturally, a number of questions remain.
但自然地，仍然存在一些问题。
On the technical side, there‘s the problem of batteries.
在技术方面，存在电池问题。
A 23-minute flight could get you across town, but how and where does the battery recharge?
23分钟的飞行可以让你穿越城市，但电池如何以及在哪里充电呢？
And regulations are a challenge too.
法规也是一个挑战。
US authorities require aircraft to carry at least 20 minutes of spare fuel.
美国政府机构要求飞机至少携带20分钟的备用燃料。
If you only have 23 or even 30 in total, that leaves very little leeway.
如果你总共只有23分钟甚至30分钟的飞行时间，那就几乎没有什么回旋余地了。
Control of access to flight paths will also need to be worked out.
飞行航线的准入控制也需要制定出来。